Hey everyone, my name is Pete Cheslock and I'm here to share with you our latest feature
in the AppMap extension for JetBrains users, Code Accurate Automatic Sequence Diagrams.
After installing the AppMap plugin to your Spring Java project, select on the Run with
AppMap icon to start your application with AppMap enabled.
After your application is running, you can create a new remote recording of an interaction.
Click the record button and enter in the URL for your application to start recording.
Now interact with your application in any way that you're trying to better understand.
When finished, click Stop Recording and name your AppMap.
You can now open your AppMap, which will default to Dependency View.
Then click over to the new Sequence Diagram view, where you can see all the interactions
from API to Database, and directly link to any of the code involved in your request.
You can get started now by downloading AppMap at appmap.io or inside your JetBrains Marketplace.